http://www.cinema.com/legal/privacy.phtml

Croods 2, TheHalf BrothersFreaky
Monsters of ManLet Them All TalkSuperintelligenceDreamland
Privacy Statement for Cinema.com:
Cinema.com has created this privacy statement to demonstrate our firm commitment to your data privacy in compliance with the General Data Protection Regulations (GDPR) and the Data Protection Act. This policy explains how we, as the Controller of your data. gather, use and protect the personal information that you give us when you sign up to www.cinema.com.
We collect website usage information using cookies. Cookies are text files placed on your computer to collect standard internet log and visitor behaviour information. We use it to track visitors' use of the website and to compile statistical reports on user activity. For further information visit www.aboutcookies.org
or www.allaboutcookies.org. Cookies do not give us access to your computer or any information about you. We do not store any of your personal information in your Cookies.
You can set your browser to not accept cookies. The above websites tell you how to decline cookies and remove them from your browser. However, in a few cases some of the functionality of our website may not operate as a result. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Website. Your IP address is also used to identify the country you are in.
Through surveys and newsletter registration, our site may request you to give us contact, location and personal information (such as your name, country and email address).
We run competitions on our site in which we ask visitors for their email address. The email address is used to notify users of new content, upcoming competitions, newsletters or if they have won a contest. You may opt-out of receiving future mailings by selecting the "unsubscribe" link at the bottom of the newsletter.
Our legal basis for processing your data is legitimate interest which is necessary to supply cinema.com's services to you. We will store your data until you unsubscribe from our services. We do not conduct any automated decision-making on your data.
Cinema.com is not intended for use by children under the age of 13. If you are under 13, you may not submit information about yourself to cinema.com.
This site contains links to other sites. Cinema.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other websites and you should read their own privacy statements.
We may serve third party advertising. In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognise a unique cookie on your browser but we do not have access to this information.
Community: this site contains message boards and news groups available to its users. We request users to give us their name, email, address and country to become a registered bulletin board user. This information is optional and not necessary to post messages. The administrator may use this information to send the user email notices. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the opt-out section below. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and users should exercise caution when deciding to disclose personal information.
As an individual, you have the following rights in regard to the data that we collect, process and store:
The right to be informed
The right of access
The right to rectification
The right to erasure
The right to restrict processing
The right to data portability
The right to object
Rights in relation to automated decision making and profiling
Should you wish to exercise any of these rights, please contact the Data Protection Officer (contact details below).
This policy was last updated on 25 May 2018 and it may change from time to time, so please check it periodically. Please contact the Data Protection Officer at Cinema.com (gavin.clements@cinema.com) if you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with the website.
Advertising
Terms & Conditions
Privacy Statement
Press
© 1999 - 2020 Cinema.com
